[{"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"What I know is that I have a close friend who's aunt disappeared in New Orleans .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"disappeared\", does the participant \"aunt\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Hundreds of people are feared dead in Mississippi , and the Louisiana city of New Orleans is badly flooded .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"flooded\", does the participant \"city\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They have unbeatable price in town and deliver on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"They\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A pattern of arrests and seizures indicate that arms are brought by the LTTE from Laos , Cambodia and Thailand into Chittagong , from where they are transported northward by land to Bhutan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"indicate\", does the participant \"pattern\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"My vet told me when a dog is vomiting a lot , it could be a sign of obstruction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"vet\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"My last son , was born in Northern Ontario ....\"\nQuestion: In the event \"born\", does the participant \"son\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I crave those .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"crave\", does the participant \"those\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Cullen and Dykman ( attorneys for Boston Gas Company ) approved all of our changes on the agreement to release the Tenn and Iroq space back to Boston Gas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"release\", does the participant \"space\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I hope you do n't change your mind about going to the wedding Sunday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the participant \"mind\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I did the same thing that you did for christmas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"thing\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"At the time , guardsmen were required to accumulate a minimum of 50 points to meet their yearly obligation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accumulate\", does the participant \"minimum\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I sent a graphic that would have been distorted if printed as it was .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"distorted\", does the participant \"graphic\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He described Allawi 's face as that of a f*ed horse and he dismissed the whole government as a band of thieves and traitors .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"described\", does the participant \"face\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Plaster of Paris does two things\"\nQuestion: In the event \"does\", does the participant \"things\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Tamils feel that the proposed defense agreement between India and Sri Lanka would encourage Sinhala rulers to prepare for another war abandoning the current peace process\"\nQuestion: In the event \"encourage\", does the participant \"agreement\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had a sampler of IPA , Brawler , Love Stout & ESA .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"sampler\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Joe removed a wasp nest for our condominium building and we appreciated the environmentally friendly method and prompt , friendly and informative service .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"appreciated\", does the participant \"we\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I hope you do n't change your mind about going to the wedding Sunday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Well , they have a variety of sports that they play like basketball , soccer , etc .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"play\", does the participant \"they\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This sounds better than the limitations you were describing in the meeting .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"describing\", does the participant \"you\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Restaurant on top was renovated , food was decent , price was way to high for Duluth for quality , new decor seems tacky\"\nQuestion: In the event \"renovated\", does the participant \"Restaurant\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bisconti wanted over $ 300 to fix my laptop and these guys fixed it for $ 90 !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"it\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"you play too much cod ;P\"\nQuestion: In the event \"play\", does the participant \"you\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"sorry , i left lou off of the message .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the participant \"i\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think they have the largest collection for Chandeliers Chicago .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The letters , six in all , were sent within two hours of each other and represented dozens of power generators .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"represented\", does the participant \"dozens\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"His artworks were selected and exhibited in British Museum in 2002 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"selected\", does the participant \"artworks\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The sample includes our \" caveat \" , so it should be fine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"includes\", does the participant \"caveat\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Phenology studies an organism 's development and life cycle -- the pulse of life .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"studies\", does the participant \"Phenology\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Another problem is that sometimes bad eggs will fungus and the fungus will spread out and kill all the eggs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"problem\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These changes are occurring across all species , Parmesan told UPI 's Climate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"Parmesan\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Another great business bites the dust !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"bites\", does the participant \"business\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Today 's incident proves that Sharon has lost his patience and his hope in peace .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"proves\", does the participant \"incident\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I swear that he might have twisted it off had I understood what it would mean to Garcia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"twisted\", does the participant \"he\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Dunn believes the resulting overcharges for electricity exceeded $ 30 billion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"exceeded\", does the participant \"$\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"You have to pay CASH ONLY before they start unloading track on your destination .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pay\", does the participant \"CASH\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These animals have the misfortune to produce a substance that is useful in the manufacture of perfume .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"produce\", does the participant \"substance\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I think he could 've done more to assuage my concerns by giving me concrete facts .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assuage\", does the participant \"concerns\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Damage estimates of more than $ 25 bn suggest it could be the US insurance industry 's most expensive natural disaster ever .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suggest\", does the participant \"estimates\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The good news is that all of this is temporary , because the evolution of international law has always adapted itself to reality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adapted\", does the participant \"itself\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"A NATO spokesman said : \" There 's no tracking mechanism to ensure they do n't fall into the wrong hands .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fall\", does the participant \"they\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The Chili Relleno .. had no batter on it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"Relleno\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Senate increases NASA funding\"\nQuestion: In the event \"increases\", does the participant \"funding\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"it runs you about 4 bucks and it deals crushing blows to hunger .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"runs\", does the participant \"bucks\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I think it will help me very much in my role .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The bottom line is that the food is n't great and is relatively high - priced .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"line\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Another problem is that sometimes bad eggs will fungus and the fungus will spread out and kill all the eggs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kill\", does the participant \"eggs\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"i satisfy your appetitie for lovin .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"satisfy\", does the participant \"appetitie\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The only problem that I had in 2 years of living there was that the walls are pretty thin , sometimes I could here my neighbors conversations .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"here\", does the participant \"conversations\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I listed all of our ( sometimes mine vs. my wife 's favorites and priorities ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"listed\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Joe removed a wasp nest for our condominium building and we appreciated the environmentally friendly method and prompt , friendly and informative service .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"removed\", does the participant \"Joe\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I work for a large retail company recently expanding our operations into Canada and had to travel to ensure all of our computer network equipment was installed properly and on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"expanding\", does the participant \"operations\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The missile 's manufacturers state that one or two missiles could cripple a destroyer , and five missiles could sink a 20,000 ton ship .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sink\", does the participant \"ship\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My assistant Joanne Rozycki has cell , car numbers to reach me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"numbers\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The US lost yet another helicopter to hostile fire near Habbaniyah in the Sunni heartland , but this time the crew was safe .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lost\", does the participant \"helicopter\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I MAKE MONEY NOT DEAL WITH BROKERS \" Wow , can you believe in today s tough times this dealership would be looking for any way to move vehicles .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"MAKE\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We need to include all outstanding transactions .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"include\", does the participant \"transactions\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The 99 - tonne cache of AK47s was to have been secretly flown out from a US base in Bosnia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"was\", does the participant \"cache\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" Across the United States , the northern edge of species ' range is expanding , \" she said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"expanding\", does the participant \"edge\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"i know you remember the bet .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remember\", does the participant \"bet\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Arial photos of the lab were uranium is being enriched , somewhat like those of chemical weapons stockpiles in Iraq .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enriched\", does the participant \"uranium\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The Americans detected the attempt to infiltrate the urban areas and were already redeploying troops from the rural areas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"infiltrate\", does the participant \"areas\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"On August 21st , 2009 I ordered furniture from Hickory Furniture Mart and contracted for HDS to deliver it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"deliver\", does the participant \"it\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"MFJ Inc transformed our run down back yard into a place of beauty .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"transformed\", does the participant \"Inc\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They interviewed me , gave me tests in the software I included on my resume , and placed me in a position that I kept for several years .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"interviewed\", does the participant \"They\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The pictures are broadcast at a rate of about 60 Hz , which is how fast they need to move for us to see them as a moving , flawless picture .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"broadcast\", does the participant \"pictures\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We all enjoy buying a snack when visiting a town or attraction while on holiday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enjoy\", does the participant \"We\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I had a routine surgery for an ingrown toenail .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Dale \" means \" river valley . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"means\", does the participant \"Dale\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"On September 21 , 2004 , the U.S. Senate Appropriations Committee approved $ 16.379 billion in funding for NASA for fiscal year 2005 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"approved\", does the participant \"Committee\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They wanted to brainwash them and control them . ''\"\nQuestion: In the event \"brainwash\", does the participant \"them\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"There 's plenty of parking , and I 've never had an issue with audience members who wo n't stop talking or answering their cellphones .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"stop\", does the participant \"members\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The other ladies had a similar experience , both had nail polish on a couple of toes .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"ladies\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Meditation has to do with what is called ideation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"Meditation\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I believe he must have waited among the gorse bushes through which the path winds and struck him down as he passed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"struck\", does the participant \"him\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"( '' We have three generations of martyrs : grandmothers , mothers , daughters . '' )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"We\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Last month , Katrina devastated refineries in Louisiana and Mississippi and sent prices to a record high of 70.85 dollars a barrel .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"devastated\", does the participant \"refineries\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Dessert was ... hmmm , that 's interesting , I do n't even remember dessert .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remember\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I was told to take my coffee to go if I wanted to finish it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"finish\", does the participant \"it\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Dr. Mann killed our pet\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"pet\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"But if -- there 's a painting on the wall in the Oval Office that shows a horseman charging up a steep cliff , and there are at least two other horsemen following .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shows\", does the participant \"horseman\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"An analysis of 65 bird species in the United Kingdom shows about one - third are laying their eggs four to seven days earlier than they did 25 years ago .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"laying\", does the participant \"third\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"America cried wolf in Iraq , and what 's scary is that sooner or later , that wolf will probably get us .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cried\", does the participant \"America\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"You need either a filter for each device except the DSL modem , or a whole home filter which filters all the jacks , except the one which the DSL modem connects .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filters\", does the participant \"filter\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They kept the name Oracle and created the RDBMS engine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"created\", does the participant \"engine\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I expect that many of the displaced people ( those affluent and those not ) will remain in the places they were evacuated to .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"evacuated\", does the participant \"they\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I got highlights , haircut , and a blowdry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I saw this place and it looked like the HOLY GRAIL .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"saw\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We heard nothing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"heard\", does the participant \"nothing\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Attached are the draft Schedule to the ISDA Master Agreement , together with Paragraph 13 to the ISDA Credit Support Annex .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"Schedule\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Arial photos , loose connections to AQ Kahn and Libya make up the evidence that the group presented .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"presented\", does the participant \"evidence\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I used my card to purchase a meal on the menu and the total on my receipt was $ 8.95 but when I went on line to check my transaction it show $ 10.74 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"used\", does the participant \"card\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Family owned and operated makes sure the atmosphere is relaxed and the food home - cooked with style .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cooked\", does the participant \"food\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"And a portion of each package or memorial purchased goes to a charity on their database .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"goes\", does the participant \"portion\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I adopted a 3.5 month old yellow lab last winter from the Dumb Friends League .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adopted\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I melt brass and cast it http://www.mikegigi.com/castgobl.htm\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cast\", does the participant \"it\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i know you remember the bet .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"i\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I Love Hellada Gallery !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Love\", does the participant \"Gallery\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"What followed the next day is considered by the governor and Dunn to be the pivotal moment of the energy crisis .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"followed\", does the participant \"What\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Across the board , the American military is stretched to the breaking point .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"stretched\", does the participant \"military\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Their Club sandwich looks tasty , maybe that 'll change my mind .... and a different server .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the participant \"mind\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I dropped the truck off in the morning and it was ready that afternoon .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dropped\", does the participant \"truck\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Exxon Mobil released nonessential staff from two giant Texas plants .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"released\", does the participant \"staff\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I know that with my industry - wide and investment banking contacts that I can help raise capital for the fund .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"raise\", does the participant \"capital\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Most experts believe China intends to develop a small space station of its own over the next several years .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"develop\", does the participant \"station\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I dropped the truck off in the morning and it was ready that afternoon .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dropped\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"About 30 seconds into his address , he started flogging the terrorist issue just one more time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"he\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They had a room with a $ 99 rate , which I booked .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"booked\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A woman walks into an Israeli restaurant in mid-day , eats , observes families with old people and children eating their lunch in the adjacent tables and pays the bill .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eating\", does the participant \"lunch\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In Texas , BP shut its 460,000 barrels per day refinery and Marathon shut its 72,000 bpd plant .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shut\", does the participant \"Marathon\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Everything was done on a timely manner and things were cleaned and picked up every day when the crew was done .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"done\", does the participant \"Everything\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We had fewer social benefits at that time for people so many immigrants were not counted .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"counted\", does the participant \"immigrants\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The days start to shorten & it gets even wetter , windier & colder .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"start\", does the participant \"days\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I did the same thing that you did for christmas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I wanted to follow up with you regarding the creation and approval of ISDA Confirmations for the following equity trades that I understand Laurel had discussed with you previously .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"understand\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This place had the worst tasting pizza I have ever tasted it was possible the worst food I 've ever eaten .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"place\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I hope you have a great summer .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Last month , Nasrallah announced that his party would close ranks with Hamas .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"close\", does the participant \"ranks\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He said it was the same tire , and verified this , after checking both the actual tire on my car and my service papers from earlier in the week .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"He\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This defeats the purpose of using a Tradename .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"defeats\", does the participant \"purpose\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think I gained three pounds in my week long cruise .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gained\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I expected to pay for this service , but imagine my surprise when I received a bill for MORE than what I paid to have the original return prepared .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"paid\", does the participant \"what\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I had this ridiculous celebrity stylist from LA named Derrick .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The work was completed within one week , and everything was cleaned up on completion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cleaned\", does the participant \"everything\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The lady at pet smart said 4 hours , but on places on the net it says 10 to 12 hours .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"hours\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Enclosed is a worksheet for Ineos Acrylics .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Enclosed\", does the participant \"worksheet\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A state Senate committee is set today to start serving 16 subpoenas on electricity producers and officials who manage California 's energy grid to determine whether they acted in concert to manipulate energy prices .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"manipulate\", does the participant \"prices\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In the Oct. 31 letters , electricity producers told federal officials that if price caps were n't removed it would lead to a collapse of the energy market .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"removed\", does the participant \"caps\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Justin , I have no knowledge of any bad faith actins Enron has pending in Texas but I will call Richard Sanders who manages domestic litgation here .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"manages\", does the participant \"Sanders\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Once upon a time ( in 2001 , to be specific ) , the Coca - Cola corporation built a bottling plant in a small and remote Indian village in the state of Kerala .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"built\", does the participant \"plant\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"First room had used tissues next to the bed and I requested it be rectified .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rectified\", does the participant \"it\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"To that regards , I noticed I was not approved to sell naked calls .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"noticed\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bangs said the agency has established viable wolf packs in the northern Rockies , as required by federal regulations .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"established\", does the participant \"packs\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I love the location and the apartment !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I need something reliable and good looking .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"something\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The ACIA -- with participation by the United States , Canada , Denmark , Finland , Iceland , Norway , the Russian Federation and Sweden -- was begun in 2000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"begun\", does the participant \"ACIA\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have to mention that i recently separated the father into another cage close to the ' nest cage ' because he and the mother were fighting .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"separated\", does the participant \"father\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"You have two screws that attach the sight to the wang .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"You\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The German Expressionist movement was destroyed as a result .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"destroyed\", does the participant \"movement\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Winter defied his own board and Gov. Gray Davis when he filed a 50 - page request to remove the caps , records and interviews show .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remove\", does the participant \"caps\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"It was incorporated as a city on May 26 , 1955 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"incorporated\", does the participant \"It\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"All he had to do for a complete victory was allow the military to go into Laos and Cambodia and finish off the shattered Communist forces .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"allow\", does the participant \"military\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"But just this week a peddle broke .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"broke\", does the participant \"peddle\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Pools The Mariner of the Seas and Liberty both had salt water pools - which most cruise ships have .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"pools\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Spring festivities include the ever - popular St Patrick 's Festival .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"include\", does the participant \"festivities\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"There are only about 850 wolves in the West , but there are an estimated 31,000 mountain lions .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the participant \"wolves\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" There is always the possibility they could jam us up , make us look like we are not numero uno , \" Pike said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Pike\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Saddam killed every month more people than all those who died from suicide murders since the Coalition occupation of Iraq .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"those\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"As a result , your finances improve - and your newfound confidence could attract new love into your life .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"improve\", does the participant \"finances\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The mysterious RAPHAEL Holinshed was named for the mysterious Neoplatonic Italian painter RAPHAEL Sanzio who painted _ St. George Fighting the Dragon _ ( 1504 - 06 )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"painted\", does the participant \"George\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Records show that on Oct. 31 , power generators and electricity traders filed letters with the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission , demanding that the new plan be killed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"plan\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Every student of political science debates how you prevent an anti-democratic force from winning a democratic election and abolishing democracy .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"winning\", does the participant \"election\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The missile 's manufacturers state that one or two missiles could cripple a destroyer , and five missiles could sink a 20,000 ton ship .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sink\", does the participant \"missiles\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i need to now get a job at house of pies b/c that is the only way to pay the bills .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pay\", does the participant \"bills\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I took the original piece of metal and rigged it to make due since I had to complete the job .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rigged\", does the participant \"it\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I interviewed several contractors for a kitchen remodel .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"interviewed\", does the participant \"contractors\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In the words of my new accountant , THEY LET ME DOWN !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"LET\", does the participant \"ME\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"MFJ Inc transformed our run down back yard into a place of beauty .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"transformed\", does the participant \"yard\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We took our beloved kitty to him and it came back dead .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the participant \"kitty\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The good news is that all of this is temporary , because the evolution of international law has always adapted itself to reality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adapted\", does the participant \"evolution\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"There is considerable evidence that it is developing both a long - range missile force and a range of weapons of mass destruction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"developing\", does the participant \"force\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"President Bush pinched a few nerves yesterday with his choice of words :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pinched\", does the participant \"Bush\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This message was cancelled from within Mozilla .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cancelled\", does the participant \"message\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The call was cancelled .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cancelled\", does the participant \"call\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"About 1,200 Indian soldiers were killed during this phase of the conflict .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"soldiers\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These changes are occurring across all species , Parmesan told UPI 's Climate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"occurring\", does the participant \"changes\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In all , we received requests for 61 persons outside of Enron to host an eSpeak event .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"received\", does the participant \"requests\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"All you have to do is become a member and watch your earnings grow !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"grow\", does the participant \"earnings\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"YOU GET WHAT YOU PAY FOR !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"PAY\", does the participant \"YOU\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The intruders slit the screen of the window .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"slit\", does the participant \"screen\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"There is a very good book on the subject that was written by General Vo Nguyen Giap .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"written\", does the participant \"book\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We need to change the Prod Description fro the LME Product .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the participant \"Description\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I had a conversation with the woman running this place in April 2010 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The prestigious IAEA ( International Atomic Energy Agency ) published an early report on Chernobyl which was based on information from Russian sources and stated that there was no significant health effects .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"published\", does the participant \"report\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have the opportunity to pick up a super nice 6 year old for free .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"opportunity\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" It may be uninteresting to a lot of people , \" Beschta told Blue Planet .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"Planet\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Brass has an even higher melting point than bronze and I would think your charcoal just does n't get hot enough .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"point\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A 1971 evaluation called Bush \" an exceptionally fine young officer and pilot \" who \" continually flies intercept missions with the unit to increase his proficiency even further . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"increase\", does the participant \"proficiency\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Loads of places have geographical hazards , if you are constantly paranoid , you 'll never get anywhere without a sense of adventure .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"Loads\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have my paralegal gathering the pleadings Enron requested .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"requested\", does the participant \"Enron\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The US lost yet another helicopter to hostile fire near Habbaniyah in the Sunni heartland , but this time the crew was safe .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lost\", does the participant \"US\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The rapid victory during the first Gulf War cemented this perception .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cemented\", does the participant \"perception\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Four guys around a large square open hibachi cook your food , and when it 's finished a server brings it to your table .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"finished\", does the participant \"it\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You review and approve it , keep it on your desk , and I will come over and make the change at your desk on Monday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"review\", does the participant \"You\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Guerrillas threatened to assassinate Prime Minister Iyad Allawi and Minister of Defense Hazem Shaalan in retaliation for the attack .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assassinate\", does the participant \"Allawi\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The latter usually consider human beings a threat but the polar bear considers humans a snack , experts said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"considers\", does the participant \"bear\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The last I checked , the Satanists have a long way to go to catch up with the death and destruction dealt out by self - proclaimed ( though false ) Christians .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"way\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In an apparently unrelated incidents , some eleven Iraqis were killed by snipers on Tuesday , including a group of police trainees in a bus near Hilla and two police in Kirkuk .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"Iraqis\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Even Zawahiri 's attorney in 1999 said that Bin Laden and Zawahiri were likely to resort to the biological and chemical agents they possessed given the extradition pressure senior Al Qaeda leaders faced .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"faced\", does the participant \"leaders\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The Rock revolution happened in the Sixties ( 6 , number of the Beast ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"happened\", does the participant \"revolution\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"That indicates that they thrive in different water chemistries .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"indicates\", does the participant \"That\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The food tasted like rat feces\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tasted\", does the participant \"food\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In London , the price of Brent North Sea crude for November delivery advanced 53 cents to 64.73 dollars .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"advanced\", does the participant \"price\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"she told me that after friday and saturday she felt i was slowly regressing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"regressing\", does the participant \"i\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The last wolf was killed in Yellowstone National Park in 1943 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"wolf\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In other words the table is set .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"set\", does the participant \"table\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The initial reservoir reports estimate reserves of 80 - 120 million barrels of sour crude and they estimate initial production to be 40,000 bpd starting in 1Q 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"estimate\", does the participant \"they\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Dr. Obina told me that his office closed at noon and that I should call him on Monday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"closed\", does the participant \"office\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Edible ones , I hope - beef , pork , chicken , fish ...\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They called and worked with me to fix it so that it would look perfect .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the participant \"it\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Police said Bernard confessed to detectives that he had sex with a young girl in November 2002 and admitted to knowing about sexual acts involving children and a dog that occurred at Hosanna Church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"involving\", does the participant \"children\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Even my PA i went to the other day said \" it must by comforting to have gone to a heart surgeon like him who will do nothing for you \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"PA\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I told Paul that you called him yesterday so abruptly because you did n't want to waste his time while you got tests done for arthritis .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"By comparison , outdoor cats have a life expectancy of 3 - 7 years depending on how many predators are in the local environment .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"cats\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I laugh and say , no , that Warwick is in New York , but I 'm at the Radison - Warwick .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"laugh\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He said the main aim of the subpoenas will be to determine whether collusion occurred to \" fix \" prices , which would violate federal trade laws .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the participant \"prices\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Should the Arctic Ocean become ice - free in summer , it is likely that polar bears and some seal species would be driven toward extinction , \" the report concluded .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"driven\", does the participant \"bears\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He eats all of his grain but it just takes him a while to get it chewed because of the lack of muscle in his jaws .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eats\", does the participant \"all\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"they have their own website which you can easily find using any search engine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"website\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" The governor believes it was the defining moment , when what was a mounting problem turned into an instant crisis , \" Maviglio said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"turned\", does the participant \"what\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The dealer wanted $ 1300 to fix that and another $ 1500 to fix some other things .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the participant \"things\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Attached is a draft of the talking points for the Commission 's hearings .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"draft\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Hyatt web site improved .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"improved\", does the participant \"site\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I work for a large retail company recently expanding our operations into Canada and had to travel to ensure all of our computer network equipment was installed properly and on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"installed\", does the participant \"all\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Attached is my draft of a request for rehearing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"draft\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"An incredible number of people in the Arab world believe that September 11 never happened , or was an American provocation or , even better , a Jewish plot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"happened\", does the participant \"September\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Who knows how much they want me to pay to fix this thing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the participant \"thing\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Iran is encircled by Afghanistan , by the Gulf States , Iraq and the Moslem republics of the former Soviet Union .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"encircled\", does the participant \"Iran\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Thou art growing less doltish and more shrewd every day , Sancho , \" said Don Quixote .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"growing\", does the participant \"Thou\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"you need to learn about white balance , composition , angle , and work on using the camera properly ...\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"you\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" They ( ISO management ) did what any independent system operator would do . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"They\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In the end Nixon kept his promise for \" . peace with honor .. \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kept\", does the participant \"Nixon\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They treat there employees with respect and concern and expect that they will extend the same politeness to there customers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"extend\", does the participant \"politeness\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Yazid Sufaat provided Moussaoui with a letter indicating that he was a marketing representative for Infocus Technologies and allegedly provided him $ 35,000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provided\", does the participant \"$\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I melt brass and cast it http://www.mikegigi.com/castgobl.htm\"\nQuestion: In the event \"melt\", does the participant \"brass\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" We applaud China 's space achievements , \" NASA spokesman Allard Beutel said Tuesday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Beutel\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"New Orleans mayor Ray Nagin said up to 80 % of the city was submerged , in some cases by waters 6 m ( 20 ft ) deep .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"submerged\", does the participant \"%\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bisconti wanted over $ 300 to fix my laptop and these guys fixed it for $ 90 !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fix\", does the participant \"laptop\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He said Mr Dar , 33 , was arrested in Indian - administered Kashmir and belonged to the outlawed Lashkar - e - Toiba militant group .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"He\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"One thought is to have just the agenda as a couple topics and then lead in with the first two questions as I 've listed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"listed\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I understand how competitive the process has become , but I felt that with my work experiences , recommendations , personality , extracurricular activities , etc. that this would compensate for my disability .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"become\", does the participant \"process\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There are several just off their beautiful beach .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the participant \"several\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In Calcutta there is a Foreigner 's reservation office where they speak English very well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"speak\", does the participant \"English\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We understand that the pipe fitters are also planning to picket the Lake Worth , Florida project as well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"planning\", does the participant \"fitters\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I saw a site that charges $ 0.70 per mile .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"saw\", does the participant \"site\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Your fellow employees asked for everyone from Britney Spears to George Bush .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the participant \"employees\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They did a vehicle wrap for my Toyota Venza that looks amazing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"wrap\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I like to imagine the thought processes going on in W 's head if he were to actually read the letter , but it is hard to picture him actually reading this letter .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"imagine\", does the participant \"processes\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have to tell you that I have n't had one and do n't want one .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The Agel compensation plan includes the principles that ensure that promise can be fulfilled for those who work at it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fulfilled\", does the participant \"promise\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Following on the heels of Ben 's annoucement yesterday , I thought I 'd post that I have joined Google as well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"joined\", does the participant \"Google\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The decor left a lot to be desired and the posters telling me all the reasons 99 was great just served as an ironic contrast against the reality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the participant \"lot\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"A state Senate committee is set today to start serving 16 subpoenas on electricity producers and officials who manage California 's energy grid to determine whether they acted in concert to manipulate energy prices .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"serving\", does the participant \"subpoenas\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I survived it without a problem .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"survived\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I put my foot in the water and it was cool .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"put\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I KNOW YOU HAVE A LOT GOING ON WITH YOU AND THE LITTLE WOMAN .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"KNOW\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In 1594 PEREZ wrote & published a book under the assumed name of \" RAPHAEL PEREGRINO . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wrote\", does the participant \"book\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Sussex have White Skin which could be recessive or dominate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"Sussex\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I used Birdies for our Annual Walk Against Drugs and Alcohol event .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"used\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The bear dwarfed the 6 - foot - 1 Mr. Parenteau , knocking him to the ground , he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dwarfed\", does the participant \"Parenteau\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"There is nothing wrong with a REAL negotiation , but nothing particularly helpful about generating one that s just for show .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"generating\", does the participant \"one\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My brother said they only had full - auto and semiautomatic during Vietnam .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"brother\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The United States was to cut its level by 7 per cent .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"was\", does the participant \"States\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"One thought is to have just the agenda as a couple topics and then lead in with the first two questions as I 've listed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"thought\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Dr Greenwalt fixed my neck from a snowboard injury and was way more effective that a regular doctor .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"neck\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Several candidates were assassinated and targeted these last two weeks , others have been forced under threats to withdraw and to follow the example of the Islamic party .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"follow\", does the participant \"example\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"What is this irish tune called !?\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"What\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The recent elections in Iraq were dominated by an amalgam of religiously fundamentalist Shi'ite organizations , principally the Dawa Party and the Supreme Council for Islamic Revolution in Iraq ( SCIRI ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dominated\", does the participant \"elections\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Previous reviewers said they were pushy and I can understand that , but I find the staff more helpful than anything else .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"reviewers\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The Jewish marriage living to the right of George 's house said that he is an arrogant person who does never return a greeting .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"marriage\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He warned water levels could still rise .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rise\", does the participant \"levels\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I presume you need the Pakistan base for rescue operations in case anything went wrong .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"presume\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I anticipate completing the review of the Master Agreement form and submitting comments to you by Monday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"completing\", does the participant \"review\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Thanks to repeated deployments to Iraq and Afghanistan , recruiting is at an all - time low .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"recruiting\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think it s only fair that nowadays every town should provide at least one halal cafe or restaurant and hopefully one day every British catering establishment will be halal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"That means making yourself known ; that means networking .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"means\", does the participant \"That\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"i think Miramar was a famous goat trainer or something .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"i\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The workers sped up and down the street with no mind to the small children playing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sped\", does the participant \"workers\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"President Bush loves him .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"loves\", does the participant \"him\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The web site is\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"site\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The difference is when the cat hisses , that means they are annoyed and they want the other cat to go away .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"difference\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The owner warned me that it was the best salsa I would ever had , and he was right .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"warned\", does the participant \"owner\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I use Miracle Cloth , they 're fantastic , just do n't use fabric softener or dryer sheets when cleaning them , it ruins their \" grabbing \" ability .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ruins\", does the participant \"ability\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Seth provides deep tissue massage which has significantly reduced the pain in my neck and shoulders and added flexibility and movement back to the area .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reduced\", does the participant \"pain\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The impacts of climate change on the region and the globe are projected to increase substantially in the years to come . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"projected\", does the participant \"impacts\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We accecpt : Visa , MasterCard , Amex , Dinner s Club / Carte Blanche , & Personal Checks / Money Orders .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accecpt\", does the participant \"We\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Climate : Humans fuss , animals adjust\"\nQuestion: In the event \"adjust\", does the participant \"animals\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"She makes every item fit you perfectly .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"makes\", does the participant \"She\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"It says business casual but I know this can be interpreted in many ways .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"interpreted\", does the participant \"this\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Nobody thinks that there will be a lot of oil and gas in this part of the world , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"he\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"No water needed ( as with tablets or capsules )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"needed\", does the participant \"water\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We need responses or direction by no later than COB on Monday , October 30 , 2000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"We\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She said a shower would be grand .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"She\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The main reason I wrote this post is to ask anyone reading this if they know of some way I can help put a stop to this Cat Holocaust .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wrote\", does the participant \"post\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Allawi 's aged cousin and the man 's wife and daughter - in - law were abducted and guerrillas threaten to behead them if the Fallujah compaign is not stopped .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"behead\", does the participant \"them\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have the opportunity to pick up a super nice 6 year old for free .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pick\", does the participant \"old\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I called and asked about the price for hair updo and the receptionist or owner who aswered the phone refused to tell me , or even just give me an approximate price range .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"aswered\", does the participant \"phone\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Israel owes the United States at least this much , in this crisis , to cease militarily unnecessary provocations and establish genuine peace .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cease\", does the participant \"provocations\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There are deals in the Aruba book so I 'm not sure why you are n't picking those up .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"picking\", does the participant \"those\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"( Participants pledged to raise at least $ 100,000 by bundling together cheques of up to $ 1,000 from friends and family .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"raise\", does the participant \"$\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The main reason I wrote this post is to ask anyone reading this if they know of some way I can help put a stop to this Cat Holocaust .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reading\", does the participant \"this\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The FBI 's profile includes a US - based supporter of the militant islamists .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"includes\", does the participant \"profile\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He looked like a great guy for your group .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"looked\", does the participant \"He\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"On the one hand , the IPN report agreed \" Climate models generally predict that the temperature rises in the Arctic will substantially exceed the global rise .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"exceed\", does the participant \"rise\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I revised the language based on our discussions and added the language concerning interest which we had both previously approved .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"revised\", does the participant \"language\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I enjoyed your recent e-mail but was sorry to hear about your dad .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enjoyed\", does the participant \"e-mail\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I work for a large retail company recently expanding our operations into Canada and had to travel to ensure all of our computer network equipment was installed properly and on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"work\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Orders for the deal to go ahead were given by the US Department of Defense .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"given\", does the participant \"Orders\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"And the President becomes a Dictator , unrestrained by anything in the Constitution , backed up by the Armed Forces , which would be entirely under his personal control .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"becomes\", does the participant \"President\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We need to change the lock and place posted signs at the gate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"place\", does the participant \"signs\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Lo and behold , they replaced the screen ( which had to be ordered ) yesterday and did n't charge me a dime .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"charge\", does the participant \"me\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The other stylists around me kept pressuring me saying he 's so wonderful , you 're going to love your hair .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kept\", does the participant \"stylists\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Above all , we need a total absolute unity and determination of the civilized world against all three circles of evil .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"unity\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Andreas Bechtolsheim built a microcomputer ; Vinod Khosla recruited him and Scott McNealy to manufacture computers based on it , and Bill Joy to develop a UNIX - based OS for the computer .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"manufacture\", does the participant \"computers\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The mind becomes strong and sharp .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"becomes\", does the participant \"mind\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"A team from the court managed to take his deposition before he died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"he\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Final authority over lifting the cap rested with the federal government .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lifting\", does the participant \"cap\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"i have a Mature male and female they are together a lot but never laid eggs as far as i know can anyone help me figure out how to make them mate\"\nQuestion: In the event \"laid\", does the participant \"eggs\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The new Centre has 4 studios planned and now boasts the largest single dance floor area in Kingston upon Hull .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"studios\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Site made !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"Site\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We tried 4 different style of donuts , they were all the same when it came to quality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tried\", does the participant \"style\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Like William Shakspere RAPHAEL ( the painter ) died on his April birthday Laura & Bridget 's day :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"RAPHAEL\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"After the split Dow Stock there are 120 shares .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the participant \"shares\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In Texas , BP shut its 460,000 barrels per day refinery and Marathon shut its 72,000 bpd plant .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shut\", does the participant \"plant\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"On the one hand , the IPN report agreed \" Climate models generally predict that the temperature rises in the Arctic will substantially exceed the global rise .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"exceed\", does the participant \"rises\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Events change everyday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"change\", does the participant \"Events\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Another problem is that sometimes bad eggs will fungus and the fungus will spread out and kill all the eggs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fungus\", does the participant \"eggs\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" There have no business being there unless they are undermining Pakistan , '' says a Pakistani official .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"says\", does the participant \"official\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At one point they told me the dog had been fixed , the next day it had n't .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"dog\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Xinhua reports that a wide range of Iraqi political forces on Tuesday condemned Sharon 's murder of Sheikh Ahmed Yassin , a religious leader of Hamas , the day before .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"condemned\", does the participant \"murder\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"i need to now get a job at house of pies b/c that is the only way to pay the bills .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"i\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This year a newspaper claimed two UK firms were involved in a deal in which thousands of guns for Iraqi forces were re-routed to al - Qaeda .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"re-routed\", does the participant \"thousands\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Al Qaeda members and sympathizers feel that the FBI 's involvement in countries like Egypt , Saudi Arabia , Pakistan , Indonesia , and the Philippines interferes with the sovereignty of those countries .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"interferes\", does the participant \"involvement\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bangs said although the number of elk has not declined very much since the wolves came back , their behavior appears markedly different .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"appears\", does the participant \"behavior\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"One witness at the Moutasaddiq trial in Germany alleged that Zarqawi had not allowed Monotheism and Holy War to share resources with al - Qaeda in the early zeroes of the 21st century .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"share\", does the participant \"resources\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Louisiana 's Governor Blanco urged residents to spend Wednesday in prayer and assured them the crisis would eventually be overcome .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assured\", does the participant \"them\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In Texas , BP shut its 460,000 barrels per day refinery and Marathon shut its 72,000 bpd plant .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shut\", does the participant \"refinery\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The missile 's manufacturers state that one or two missiles could cripple a destroyer , and five missiles could sink a 20,000 ton ship .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cripple\", does the participant \"missiles\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I came to find out the person was the hotel OWNER also .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"came\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"James Bateman came the day I called and fixed the problem quickly and efficiently .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"problem\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Brass melts at just under 2000 F which is a bright yellow heat , not red hot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"melts\", does the participant \"Brass\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I got this .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"this\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"It boggles the mind that ANYONE can take at face value Bush 's claims to be a christian , yet many seem to do just that .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"boggles\", does the participant \"mind\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"ALITO filed a dissenting opinion , in which SCALIA and THOMAS joined as to Parts I through III .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filed\", does the participant \"ALITO\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have a few entities that may need to change groups or be assigned to a group .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"entities\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They said they were \" unable to tell me until they ordered my dress \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the participant \"dress\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It 's become a guardian of morality -- not church morality ; real morality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"become\", does the participant \"It\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"All he had to do for a complete victory was allow the military to go into Laos and Cambodia and finish off the shattered Communist forces .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"finish\", does the participant \"forces\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Despite the name , this entity appears to be a MTM company .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"appears\", does the participant \"entity\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They said that we were to be charged for this room regardless because we did not cancel within the 72 hours .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"They\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"and around what time they eat each of their meals .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eat\", does the participant \"each\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The intruders slit the screen of the window .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"slit\", does the participant \"intruders\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There was a change made in the coding for the delta position and this has somehow messed up the liq value .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"messed\", does the participant \"value\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Plus , I work with Janet a lot so she may get some comfort from that , instead of having a lawyer she has n't dealt with initial it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dealt\", does the participant \"she\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The millions who died in the Iran - Iraq war had nothing to do with Israel .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"millions\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The mass murder happening right now in Sudan , where the Arab Moslem regime is massacring its black Christian citizens , has nothing to do with Israel .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"massacring\", does the participant \"citizens\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"they fixed my garage doors in literally less than an hour .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"doors\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I detect the hissing lisp of the lying serpent in this article .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"detect\", does the participant \"lisp\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I ordered 1000 postcards , we normally order 5000 or more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the participant \"I\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We recommend these cabins !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"recommend\", does the participant \"cabins\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The bombings implicated Muslims , and exacerbated regional tensions which the Bush regime and its friends wearing the brass in the Philippine military sought to exploit .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"implicated\", does the participant \"bombings\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"<< Upon the sixth of April , Alexander the Great was born .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"born\", does the participant \"Alexander\" change in state?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He gave no service to anyone , risked nothing , and did not even slack off efficiently .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gave\", does the participant \"service\" change in state?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He vacated the FWS decision to downgrade the wolf 's status .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"downgrade\", does the participant \"status\" change in state?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}]